[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
hey folks David Tao with barbend.com and
today we're talking about how to watch
the 2023 Noble CrossFit Games it's in
Madison Wisconsin once again
temperatures are supposed to be hot the
athletes are supposed to be fit and the
crowd is supposed to be well a
combination of fit and maybe a little
too sunburned so make sure to pack your
sunscreen but if you're watching at home
we've got exactly how to stay tuned into
all the action
the 2023 Noble CrossFit Games run in
Madison Wisconsin from August 1st
through August 6th that's Tuesday
through Sunday but not all divisions
compete every day
age group that includes teens and
Masters and adaptive divisions compete
on Tuesday Wednesday and Thursday and
winners from those divisions are crowned
on Thursday team and individual
competition takes place Thursday through
Sunday and the winners of those
respective divisions are crowned on
Sunday evening
the best places to tune in for Live
Action like live actual footage of the
2023 Noble CrossFit Games our
games.crossfit.com and the CrossFit
Games app historically CrossFit has
actually streamed the games and most of
the individual and team events on
YouTube and then embedded that or
syndicated that on the GameStop
crossfit.com website we have no
indication that it'll be anything
different this year the nice thing about
that is you can follow along live or you
can get the footage ready even just a
few hours later if you're playing a
little bit of catch-up for example if
you have work or any other fun summer
activities you're up to
let's talk about time zones Madison
Wisconsin is on Central time so the full
schedule of the takes place on local
time Central time so if you're in New
York like me that's an hour behind so
when exactly do events take place each
day well action according to the
officialgames.crossfit.com schedule
kicks off at 10 A.M every day Tuesday
through Sunday now that doesn't actually
mean each and every event or each and
every day will start at 10 A.M but that
is the beginning of the window of
possible events that could occur on each
day according to the official schedule
action runs well it's a little different
every day it ends as early as 5 PM local
time or as late as 9 pm local time
that's on Friday oftentimes Friday
events tend to go a little later a
little more spectator friendly if you
will now those are just time ranges it's
worth noting that for the CrossFit games
all the events aren't released ahead of
time some are teased ahead of time if
you check out barbin.com we've been
writing about some events that have been
leaked maybe purposely leaked or just
spoiled by CrossFit Games on social
media but as far as the actual rundown
of exactly what's happening each day to
each and every event that's always a
mystery sometimes until just a few
minutes before the event actually starts
so CrossFit gives these time ranges as
far as win events may occur but they're
always a little mysterious as to exactly
which events are occurring when and
exactly how many events are occurring
for individuals and teams expect it to
be somewhere between 11 and 13 events
over the four days of their competition
[Music]
there you have it folks that's how to
watch the 2023 Noble CrossFit games for
Live Action games.crossfit.com and the
CrossFit Games app on your mobile device
for written coverage I'd highly
recommend checking out barbad.com we'll
have coverage Tuesday through Sunday and
just a reminder age group and adaptive
divisions are Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
that's August 1st through 3rd and
individuals of teams Thursday through
Sunday August 3rd through 6th hope you
all enjoy we'll be tuning in and
watching very closely